goldscreen.com 2017-06-04

# Privacy Policy - Goldscreen - English

goldscreen.com is fully committed to protecting the privacy of all visitors to its website.

The Privacy Policy (hereinafter “the policy”) provided below is with respect to our use and protection of any personal information you provide to us through the goldscreen.com website. Gold Screen, LLC is the sole owner of the website www.goldscreen.com (hereinafter “website”). The Policy is applicable to the website. You may be required to provide personally identifiable information at several different points on our website. By accepting the policy at the time of registration, you expressly approve and consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Policy.

Information Collection  
You can visit/surf our website without providing any personal information. However, if you choose to avail of certain services on our website, you shall be required to provide certain information for the registration and/or access to such services/web pages. Such information may include, without limitation, your name, email address, contact address, mobile/telephone number(s), sex, age, occupation, interests, financial information, content, IP address, standard web log information and such other information as may be required for your interaction with the services.

Use  
If you choose to provide us with the abovementioned information, you consent to the use, transfer and storage of the information so provided by you on our servers. The information provided by you shall not be sold/given/rented to third parties (third parties for this purpose do not include our group / holding / subsidiary companies and or our service partners / associates) for marketing purposes and other related activities without your prior consent.

The information provided by you shall be used by us to:

  * Improve our website and enable us to provide you the most user-friendly experience which is safe, smooth and customized;
  * Improve and customize our services, content and other commercial /non – commercial features on the website;
  * Send you information on our products, services, special deals, promotions;
  * Send you service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so;
  * Resolve disputes, if any and troubleshooting;
  * Provide service updates and promotional offers related to our services/products.
  * Comply with any court judgment / decree / order / directive / legal & government authority /applicable law;
  * Investigate potential violations or applicable national & international laws;
  * Investigate deliberate damage to the website/services or its legitimate operation;
  * Detect, prevent, or otherwise address security and/or technical issues;
  * Respond to Claims of third parties;

Account Protection  
Your password is the key to your account. You shall be solely responsible for all the activities happening under your username and you shall be solely responsible for keeping your password secure. Do not disclose your password to anyone. If you share your password or your personal information with others, you shall be solely responsible for all actions taken under your username and you may lose substantial control over your personal information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password.

Security  
The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter your personal information we treat the data as an asset that must be protected and use tools (encryption, passwords, physical security, etc.) to protect your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security nor can we guarantee that third parties shall not unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, and that other users may abuse or misuse your personal information that you provide. Therefore, although we work hard to protect your information, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.

Aggregate Information  
goldscreen.com uses a web statistics program to track aggregate usage of this site. This program is used to enable us to improve and expand the site. It does not allow us to personally identify individual users to the site.  
goldscreen.com does not provide any aggregate information to third parties concerning visitors to this site..

Advertising  
goldscreen.com use a few third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Changes in this Privacy Statement  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement and such other places we deem appropriate so that you are updated about the manner we collect information, what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

Any questions or clarifications with respect to this Policy can be sent to : info@goldscreen.com
